[Genius Girlfriend]
[Episode 12]
Okay, class is over.
[Reading Corner]
Remember to revise at home.
Class, don't rush off just yet.
Director.
[Reading Corner]
I have good news to share.
Today, the school
received an invitation
to invite Lin Zhixia
from Class 1, Grade 10
to attend the Marine Science Seminar
next month.
The Marine Science Seminar
offers tremendous value.
Many experts and scholars in the field
will be there.
Lin Zhixia's article
has been chosen by them.
The organizer has
asked her to share and exchange insights
as a student representative.
This is the invitation.
Lin Zhixia, come here.
Class,
let us encourage and cheer for
Lin Zhixia with our applause.
[Constantly Strive to Become Stronger;
Strive to Be Number One]
Thank you, Director.
All the best.
Class dismissed.
[Invitation]
Lin Zhixia, you are so energetic.
We had such a busy
school anniversary week,
but you still had time
to do research.
It's an old article
I previously published.
I didn't expect it to be chosen.
Lin Zhixia, congratulations.
My mom always asked me
to go to this event.
I'll go with you this year.
You're going too?
[Awards Board]
Yeah.
That's great.
I was just feeling a little nervous.
I've never presented at a seminar before.
How about this?
My mom's at the lab this weekend.
You can ask her for advice.
Okay.
[Awards Board]
Duan!
Have a soda, my treat.
Why?
It's on me.
Here, take it.
Is it poisoned?
Your side profile is amazing.
Look at that jawline.
Ma'am.
Are you sick?
Just tell me what you want.
It's not a big deal.
Well,
I think the way you tossed the ball
the other day was...
It was very...
Get to the point.
Can you get me a signed photo
of Han Geng?
Why?
Zhao Shuran from the next class
insists that I got scammed.
She said those who went to the concert
all got the signature.
She was right.
You were scammed.
I...
I don't want to lose face.
Please help me.
I have no choice.
I'm willing to spend more money.
I need it fast.
Ma'am,
with what money?
Didn't you treat us to the amusement park
with the money we got back for you?
Yes...
If I had enough money,
would I be asking you for help?
The Trendy Shop behind our school
is selling Han Geng's signed photo
for 800 per photo.
Can I afford that?
Duan, I know you have many connections
and tricks up your sleeve.
I'm sure you can get me
a signed photo.
Right?
Please.
Please...
Please!
Stop,
stop!
Stop it.
No.
I think you're out of your mind.
Duan Qiyan!
Didn't I ask nicely enough?
I used to think you were a loyal guy.
Well, I was wrong.
When you were young, you came to my house
and got beaten up by your dad.
You even ate my food.
Did I ever complain about that?
Also,
once you left a bottle of tadpoles
at my place
and they all turned into toads.
It took me forever to catch them.
If I lose out
in front of Zhao Shuran,
I'll never go to school again.
See you never.
Wait.
Now that's the Tang Tingting I know.
That act just now...
"Please..."
Why were you acting cute?
It's just an autograph.
I'll help you.
Duan!
Hands off.
Your treat.
Class,
today, we're studying
[Constantly Strive to Become Stronger;
Strive to Be Number One]
"My Castle in the Air."
This prose
adopts a writing style that combines
both reality and imagination.
The mountain cabin
is a real dwelling place.
That's realism.
It's also a spiritual resting place.
That's imaginative writing.
I'm so nervous.
It's okay.
I'm here with you.
It symbolizes the balance
between materiality and ideals.
Understand?
What are you doing
instead of paying attention?
Yes, you.
Duan Qiyan.
I've just explained
the prose, "My Castle in the Air."
Now, summarize for me
the characteristics of the prose.
What characteristics?
This one.
[Han Geng]
Duan Qiyan.
What did I say just now?
I was wondering why you couldn't improve
your language test scores.
So you're focused on this instead?
What did you write here?
Han Geng?
Autograph?
Seriously.
Duan Qiyan,
aren't you going to take
the college entrance exam?
Are you planning to be a star?
Are you?
Is that it?
Be quiet.
Stop laughing.
Let's continue.
Tang Tingting.
Long time no see.
Have you been avoiding me?
No.
Haven't you brought Han Geng's
signed photo yet?
I did.
It's in the folder I keep
in the bag drawer in my classroom.
Liars tend to embellish details.
You don't believe me?
Follow me to the classroom, then.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Lesson time.
I'll show it to you next time.
Boss.
I came to the store a while ago
and asked about
Han Geng's signed photo.
Do you remember?
I remember. What's up?
It's kind of embarrassing.
I really want to buy that signed photo.
Can you sell it to me first?
I'll work part-time for you every day
after school in return.
The salary amount is up to you.
Don't worry.
I'm very eloquent.
Hiring me is definitely worth it.
I can see that.
But you're too late.
Han Geng's signed photo has been sold.
Sold?
Okay.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[New shoes in stock]
How about this?
My mom's at the lab this weekend.
You can ask her for advice.
Lin Zhixia.
Why are you here?
I remember you'd be at
Professor Shen's lab today.
I happened to be in the neighborhood.
It's raining.
I thought you might not have an umbrella,
so I stopped by to check.
Thank you, my savior.
Let's go.
Lin Zhixia,
what would you have done
if I didn't come by today?
Continue with my experiment
and go home after the rain stops.
What if the rain never stops?
That's meteorologically impossible.
The total amount of rain
on Earth is constant.
After the rainwater evaporates,
new clouds will form.
It won't pile up infinitely.
If it keeps raining,
The atmospheric pressure will compress
these raindrops into fog.
In the end, it will form a vast,
foggy state of chaos.
Then we'd all drown in it.
That's not what I meant.
Then what are you referring to?
I mean,
if it keeps raining,
and you have to ask someone for help.
Who would you ask?
Security.
There should be an umbrella
in the security room.
What if the security is not there?
I'll ask my seniors in the lab for help.
I'll walk them back to their dorms first,
and ask them to lend me the umbrella.
What if they are all not around?
I can't possibly let you come all this way
just to pass me an umbrella.
Right.
Luckily, I happened to pass by today.
♪ Wandering light wind
drifts past your pupils ♪
♪ One second of encounter,
heartstrings stirred ♪
Then I really am lucky.
♪ The story feels altogether different ♪
♪ How to describe
my whimsical wandering dream? ♪
♪ You softly answer my quirky side ♪
♪ Such bliss to finally be understood ♪
And I called
Duan Qiyan's handwriting ugly...
Mine is even worse.
Tang!
Tang, hurry up.
Come down. What are you doing?
Why are you looking for me at this hour?
Do I need a reason to see you?
Obviously, you have one. Get to the point.
Actually,
it's not a big deal.
I just happen to have
prepared a small gift for you.
But I think it's more sincere to give
gifts in person.
So I came to you.
Open it.
What is it? So mysterious.
Just open it up.
Hurry up.
[Han Geng]
The signed photo!
Where did you get it?
Who do you think I am?
This is
a piece of cake to me.
Getting this signed photo
is as easy for me
as getting full marks on an exam.
Didn't you tell me
you wanted Han Geng’s autograph?
So I asked
one of my many bros.
He is part of the industry.
He has some connections.
I told him
I wanted an autograph of Han Geng,
[Han Geng]
and he agreed.
So,
he asked Han Geng for it.
But there was a problem.
What was the problem?
Didn't you notice my shoes?
These are the new shoes
I bought for this performance.
The shop owner of the Trendy Shop
behind our school
[New shoes in stock]
raised his offer to 1,000 yuan
to buy my shoes.
But I declined it.
But you know
who Han Geng is.
He's the hottest and best star now.
Throughout the whole process,
my execution
and calculation
were nothing short of brilliant.
Duan Qiyan, you big idiot!
Shouldn't she be happy?
Did I say something wrong?
[A hundred-year undertaking
begins with education]
[A New Chapter, A New Journey]
Tang Tingting.
So you knew that
I sold my sneakers
to buy you the signed photo?
Now that my sneakers are back...
You returned the signed photo?
How will you brag to Zhao Shuran now?
Well...
When did I brag?
I'm an honest person, okay?
Besides, no need for an overkill.
I don't need a signed photo
to outdo Zhao Shuran.
You, on the other hand,
act like you're soulless
without these shoes.
Can you stop being so childish?
Correction.
These are not shoes.
This is classic.
Classic. Whatever.
I've returned your stinky shoes.
We're even now.
Stinky.
Does it smell?
It doesn't.
It smells good.
Ms. Tang.
Congratulations.
I told you.
Our class is full of hidden talents.
Congrats to you, too.
A participation award is still an award.
Unfortunately, your class's award
has nothing to do with you.
All you did was clap on the side.
Do you know what a team is?
Tang Tingting.
You haven’t shown me
Han Geng’s signed photo yet.
Are you going to say
you left it in class again?
Are you going back to class?
I’ll go with you.
Zhao Shuran, you are so weird.
You knew I was scammed, right?
Isn't it miserable to just
hold it in and wait
for me to slip up?
You...
Yes, I didn't go to the concert.
So what?
My classmates were so worried about me.
They sneaked into the QQ group
to find the trading location.
After they found me,
we caught that scalper
on Tieba together.
Let me tell you,
so many fans wanted to gift me a banner.
I said, "No, no.
We're doing this for the people.
It's a given."
Tang Tingting,
quit spouting the nonsense you dreamed up.
I bet this would be a good dream for you.
After helping the people,
Lin Zhixia found the best place
outside the venue for us
to listen to the concert together.
It was much more interesting
than watching it in the stadium.
We lay on the grass together.
Above us, a sky full of stars.
And by our ears, Han Geng's singing.
Have you ever experienced it?
I've never seen anyone
who's so proud to be scammed.
Yes.
I was afraid you would find out
that I was scammed.
That would make me look stupid.
But I've figured it out these days.
I think it's more stupid
to feel this fear.
So what if I tell you now?
I feel much better.
Zhao Shuran,
you should find a new topic
to talk to me now.
Wait.
No one talks to you
except for me, right?
You...
You have no friends.
Consider changing your personality.
[A hundred-year undertaking
begins with education]
The impact o-of marine pollution
h-has already attracted
widespread attention.
But today,
I-I want to specifically discuss
the impact of
m-microplastic.
Currently, microplastic
h-has...
What are you doing?
Zeqiu, I'm stuttering.
Stuttering?
I have to present at the seminar tomorrow,
but now I stutter the moment I speak.
I can't tell you're stuttering at all.
Come and listen.
Let me see what the problem is.
Hello, everyone.
I'm today's high school student
representative, Lin Zhixia.
Today, I...
Today I want to talk about the impact of
mi...
m-microplastic...
r-rubbish...
on marine pollution.
Wait.
You don't usually talk like this.
I don't know either.
I get nervous whenever
I think of the speech.
Try again.
One more time.
Actually,
the pollution o-of plastic waste
h-has already drawn widespread concern.
That's enough.
Alright, alright.
What kind of problem is this?
I finally understand why Jiang Yubai
stuttered when he first saw me.
What should I do?
I can't help with this.
Nope. Can't help you.
You can't leave.
You're stuttering. It's a condition.
I can't cure it.
Please help me.
I can't help you.
Zeqiu, please help me.
My presentation is tomorrow.
I'm going to discuss with the experts
on behalf of high school students.
Professor Shen gave me this chance.
I can't screw it up no matter what!
Zeqiu!
I need someone to practice on.
If you listen to my presentation,
you can give me feedback.
If I do well,
wouldn't you be happy, Zeqiu?
Yes.
Aren't you talking quite well right now?
Right?
Relax.
Just persuade others the way
you persuade me.
Take your time.
A seminar is basically
just people chatting.
Like how we're chatting.
Okay?
One more time.
Zeqiu, please help me.
My presentation is tomorrow.
I'm going to discuss with the experts
on behalf of...
Wait, wait, wait.
Read your script.
Zhixia, did you bring everything?
Zhixia,
bring these 2 eggs with you.
Eat them if you're hungry while traveling.
You'll be living alone out there.
You really don't need us to accompany you?
It's fine, I'm just going to the suburbs.
Okay. Take this money.
Keep it close and don't lose it.
Food and accommodation are covered.
I don't need to spend money.
Doesn't hurt to be prepared.
Take it.
Keep it properly. Don't lose it.
Why are you up?
Let me send her there, Mom.
You will?
I will.
Alright.
I'm leaving, Mom.
Be careful.
Don't sleep in the car. Be alert.
When you're out and about,
nothing is more important than safety.
You must lock the door.
Got that?
[Healthy Living]
Don't just lock the door.
Lock up whatever chain lock or bolt lock
you can find on the door too.
Got that?
Wang Tao.
Last summer vacation,
they went on a family vacation.
When they checked in,
they learned that a fire once broke out
in the hotel,
killing dozens of people.
But they didn't take it seriously
and moved in.
That night,
his mother and his sister
were in the same room.
At 3 a.m.,
his mother was fast asleep.
His sister was awakened
by the sound of knocking.
Knock...
It sounded like someone was carefully
knocking on the door with their knuckles.
Isn't Wang Tao your
primary school classmate?
Yes, that Wang Tao.
I thought he had a brother.
How did it become a sister?
It was a sister all along.
You remembered wrongly.
Let me continue.
His sister got up to check
who was outside the door.
[Healthy Living]
At that moment,
the sound of knocking stopped.
His sister thought she had misheard,
and went back to bed.
But the moment she lay down,
the knocking started again.
Knock, knock, knock!
His sister looked outside
through the peephole.
There was no one outside,
but the light in the corridor was on.
At this moment,
she made a very wrong decision.
She opened the door.
Suddenly!
A gust of cold wind poured in,
accompanied by a burnt smell.
His sister rushed to bed
and continued sleeping.
When she woke up the next morning,
guess what they found.
What did they find?
They found black handprints
all over her bed.
It was as if those who died in the fire
wiped their hands all over the sheets.
Because she opened the door,
they were allowed inside.
This story
tells us that when one is out and about,
we must lock the door
and never open it for anyone.
This story tells us that
you need to be logical
when making up stories.
You're really bad at telling stories.
No, this really happened.
Really?
Really.
It really happened?
Just ask Wang Tao.
Wang Tao?
Wang Tao.
The sound of knocking was slow and light.
Knock... Knock...
It sounded like someone was carefully
knocking on the door with their knuckles.
Who is it?
When she asked who was outside the door,
the sound of knocking suddenly stopped.
His sister looked outside
through the peephole,
but there was no one outside.
At this moment,
she made a very wrong decision.
She opened the door.
Suddenly!
[Unknown Number]
Hello, Lin Zhixia.
How did you know it was me?
I guessed.
Hello.
Please
tell the guest in Room 3021
that her friend
left something for her at her door.
[Do Not Disturb]
The seminar happens tomorrow morning.
I thought I'd be kept up by excitement,
not nervousness.
And I keep hearing noises
outside the door.
Lin Zhixia,
you're not nervous.
You're scared, right?
Looks like I'm right.
I admit
I'm a little scared.
It's empty here
and too quiet.
Then...
Are you afraid of the universe?
No.
But the universe is also silent.
I understand now.
My fear comes from the unknown.
I know what the universe is like,
so I'm not afraid of it.
So, silence itself is not scary,
right?
You're right.
Hello?
Hello.
Room 3021's line is currently occupied.
We'll inform them later.
Okay, thank you.
Occupied?
Lin Zhixia, go to bed early.
You have a presentation tomorrow.
Don't be scared, I won't hang up.
Good night, Jiang Yubai.
Good night.
Lin Zhixia.
Hello?
Hello.
Room 3021's line is still occupied.
Do you still need me to call for you?
Is the line always occupied?
Yes.
How about this?
We'll try to contact them
every once in a while.
We'll let you know
when it gets through, okay?
Okay, thank you.
You're welcome.
Jiang Yubai.
Why are you awake?
Just sleep a little longer.
Okay.
Lin Zhixia!
Lin Zhixia, I'm here!
Jiang Yubai!
Jiang Yubai, are you still there?
Yes.
Did you stay up all night?
Are you still scared?
A little.
But with you here,
I'm not afraid anymore.
Why are you...
Can I hang up now?
[In Call]
When we were young,
we had to do something crazy
to live up to our youth.
For me,
I could stay up all night
to stare at microplastic
under the microscope
and find charm in something boring.
Because his friend was afraid of silence,
he could
spend the entire night listening
to the air conditioner all night long.
Someone could sacrifice
his favorite sneakers
to fulfill his friend's wishes.
At that time, we thought
these actions were impulsive
and passionate.
[Han Geng]
When we grew up, we realized that
it was the silent source of energy
powering all original aspirations.
The passion of youth can outlast time.
[Study Plan]
From today to tomorrow,
to forever.